creating that clarity. We can't jump off
sides on third and five. But what I will
say in spite of all that, they found a
way to be at their best in the most
important moments. You get the kick
blocked, they end up scoring, and then
Matthew orchestrates an unbelievable
drive. A bunch of guys made a big time
bunch of plays. You know, what a play by
Kennata Mumfield on second and 10 to be
able to get us a first down. And then
Kobe Parkinson, what a stud. I mean,
Matthew adding trust against a really
good player one-on-one on the front
pylon and and uh he goes up and gets it
and it's been kind of part for the
course. You know, Matthew trusting his
guys, guys delivering in the critical
moments and uh really grateful. And then
unbelievable job by our defense. Good
job by the kickoff coverage to be able
to pin them deep and then to be able to
go four straight plays where they don't
even get a single yard. Um awesome job
by the defense right there. Proud of the
way that we finished. Excited to be able
to clean up a lot of things. You
>> talked about Matthew's resolve a lot.
So, uh, just what did you notice out of
him those two drives to score when he's
down, just the way he played and the way
he managed.
>> I think you just said it, Nate, kind of
with your question. You know, he was
just in total command, total control.
They did a bunch of good things. You
know, I got a ton of respect for Ejiro.
Their players, you know, made it made it
difficult. Um, got some good players on
the perimeter that ended up being pretty
active. They they brought a little bit
more pressure, which kind of had been an
uptick in their, you know, um, identity
over the last couple weeks, but, uh, he
was steady. It was MVP type of stuff
what he did. Nate uh just you know good
calm. I thought he redirected a couple
of the protections that allowed him not
to be hot where we would have been and
and uh on all those plays. He ended up
finding completions and he got a bunch
of different guys involved. I thought he
saw the field really well and that's why
we're advancing because of his
leadership.
>> Was he through something?
>> You know, you'll have to talk to him
about it. I mean, he got it banged up. I
mean, you could see him shaking. Um but
he delivered a pretty damn good throw on
the very next play that our guy will
typically make that one. Um but you'll
have to he'll be better equipped to
answer that one for you.
>> All of these games this year that were
very similar to this you guys lost.
>> Yeah.
>> And did you were you thinking about that
on that final drive?
>> You know I wasn't thinking about that. I
was thinking about that. I'm really glad
that we had a lot of those moments where
we talked about our scars being our
strength and um you know fortunately we
were able to be at our best in those
most important moments and all three
phases were collectively involved in
that. You go down four points you say
all right get the ball back. Now let's
see. It was a decent return by Ronnie,
too. That puts us in, you know, not bad
field position. Matthew takes us right
down the field. You think, man, maybe we
gave him a little bit too much time.
Good coverage by the kickoff team to be
able to pin him inside the 30. Um, and
then like I said, four and out with the
defense. Here we go, man. You guys got
to listen to me talk for another week.
>> And Sean talked about Matthew's
calmness.
>> Not as funny as I used to be, huh? Can I
get is this thing on? I said
>> you talked about how calm he was on that
final. Can you describe where you were
in that final drive with him?
>> Yeah, I I think we were both, you know,
just you're just immersing yourself in
the moment. I think in a lot of
instances when I'm watching games, I'm
like with some of my close friends or uh
you know, you get more nervous watching
that than you don't have a time to
really just think about it. You just
immerse yourself, see the game one play
at a time, try to put the players in a
position to have successful outcomes and
you're not thinking about anything else.
You're kind of just in that moment. And
I could feel Matthew and I were on the
same page and he did such a great job.
Um, I did feel really good that you knew
you had four downs. Um, never even got
to that point where we needed to even
really get it to a third down, but he
was he was outstanding.
>> Sean, how do you separate how do you
separate the uh
>> I'll come right back to you, Sam.
>> Go ahead, Sam.
>> And then the pass break.
>> That was such a big play. I'm glad you
asked about that. I mean, gets the pass
break up. Kairen does a great job
converting on converting on the fourth
and one. Um, and then we end up being
able to punch that thing in with Kiran
on the little option route, which was a
great job by him on a second and six.
And so, um, which was, you know, Puka
did a great job getting a tough four
yards on the jet sweep on the previous
play. So, um, he's just, he's a freaking
warrior. I mean, you know, he's welld
deserving of being voted unanimously as
an allpro. That's how he's played for
us. And he just responds. You know, even
that one drop, you know, he was he's so
hard on himself, but he comes back, he
makes the plays. That pass breakup was
unbelievable. And it's what great
players do is they just play the next
play. Love him. Grateful that he's on
our squad.
>> You guys had some chances in [snorts]
the first half to kind of really
separate yourself and didn't obviously.
>> Yeah.
>> How do you when you look at all the
great things you did on the stretch? How
do you separate when you go and analyze
this game as you go home?
>> Well, I think you be honest about it.
You know, I I I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to cut you off. Did you finish? Yeah. I
mean, you give Carolina credit. You
know, they did a good job of being able
to kind of make it difficult for us.
They scored. Um Bryce was able to make
some plays with his legs um to kind of
extend and and create a little bit off
schedule and then you know we end up
starting the half three and out. Um they
had a good pass break up and then they
end up you know having a free runner on
the second down and then we don't
convert on the third down. So you give
them credit but man I'm so grateful to
be able to have the learning
opportunities in spite of us being able
to win this game because we are going to
need to be able to play better if we
expect to be able to advance um past
this round. But never take it for
granted. Grateful to be able to have
another week with this team that I love.
earlier about some of the difficulties
they gave you on the perimeter. Their
corners have been playing really well
all season. Um you guys started
switching back to the middle of the
field and and attacking there. What was
what were those adjustments like? What
did you see there that maybe left?
>> It was a give and take based on some of
the different coverages and you know
Jackson and Horn are as good of a tandem
as there is and um you know and then
when Horn ended up going out you know
you you bring another guy in. But um I
thought our guys made the plays that
they needed to and they made their
plays. That's what great players do.
that's what you love about this league.
But, um, ultimately the players did a
nice job. And there was some times that,
um, they were playing a little bit of
shell and we tried to be able to attack
the inside part of the field and had
some successful outcomes. And then there
was some times where I'll look at myself
and say, "Man, I wish I did a better job
of putting our guys in a, you know, a
more advantageous spot." And, um, I'll
be kicking myself for that. And
hopefully don't make those same mistakes
next week. All right. Thank you guys.
Appreciate it.
Kobe Turner and Nate Landon both saying
44 left on the clock. There was never a
doubt in their mind. Can you tell us
what the mind process was for you in
that last couple minutes?
>> Uh yeah, I mean I knew we have four
downs obviously. Um,
that's a situation I've been in a bunch
of times in my life and I was just going
to go out there and try to execute, give
our guys chances to make plays. They
made some great ones. Um, I'm glad our
guys felt that way. Um, try to continue
to prove um, that you can go out there
and do those situ, you know, do those
things and come away with with wins for
your team. So, just happy to to do my
part there at the end and and make sure
we score some points.
>> Benny, what are you feeling in a moment
like that?
>> Pretty calm. U, pretty steady. just felt
like I was seeing the coverages really
well. Guys up front did a hell of a job
keeping me clean on that last drive too.
Giving me time to click through some
progressions and um you know I feel like
uh like I said I've been in that spot a
lot in my life and so uh bring a smile
to my face cuz I like being there and um
would love to be up you know 14 and
taking a knee on it with you know four
minutes left but uh
shoot wins a win.
>> I know it's a playoff game but there
[clears throat] extra satisfaction
winning like that after the way the game
ended last year. Oh, it was not a
thought in my mind at all, you know. Um,
no. Um, had plenty of opportunities,
like I said, um, both playoffs,
non-playoffs, to go out there and try to
help our team win. I just, you know,
want to want to go back to work with
these guys. Um, you know, in the NFL,
your team changes every single week or
I'm sorry, every single year. And, um,
I'm not ready for that one to end yet.
So, I I just love going to work with
this group. Um, and and just trying to
do everything I can to make sure that we
keep getting that opportunity.
>> What was it like seeing Puka have the
impact he did today? And also just
[clears throat] beyond that touch.
>> Yeah, I mean Puka, you know, did today
what he's done kind of all year for us.
He's been unbelievable. Um, you know,
handed it to him a couple times. Uh,
made some big plays in the past game as
well. Great blocking. I thought Tay was
really good. Um, you know, missed him on
a couple offs. I had one shot down the
field and missed him and and uh, you
know, a couple things here or there, but
I thought his presence was really was
big for us as well, especially on that
last drive, just finding some catches
for us. So, um, I thought our skill
group played really well. Tight ends
play great. And then, you know, Colby,
um, you know, made a big time catch. Um,
it was pretty tight coverage. Thought I
put the ball in a good spot and, uh, he
made a great play. He was so confident
he caught it. I was like, I don't know.
Is he in? Did he catch it? He was right
on that damn pylon. I'm like, I don't
know. But he was he was hyped up like he
knew he caught it for a touchdown. So, I
was, you know, uh, kind of holding my
celebration for a little bit, but uh,
happy that he came down with it.
Matthew, you've had a lot of
>> how I say soft they played on that last
series defensively.
>> No, I feel like, you know, they were
giving us some space um throughout the
game, you know, and and um one reason or
another, we didn't hit all of them, you
know, had some opportunities and and
missed a few. Um but uh no, I think uh
you know, our tempo was great. I thought
we were keeping the ball in play. Um you
know, and just trying to trying to
distribute the field. Never surprised by
anything in this league to be honest
with you.
>> You've had a lot of comebacks.
[clears throat]
drives in your career. Obviously, the
numbers are there. How much do you enjoy
those moments and and how do you avoid
it being stressful moments? Obviously
very calm in those moments.
>> Yeah, I mean I think just experience um
belief in myself and belief in my
teammates really. Um you know, I trust
all those guys to go out there and make
plays. I just try to put it in a good
spot for those guys. But I've been in
that spot a lot in my life. I said that
earlier, but um I I love that spot. I'd
rather be, you know, me having to go out
there with our offense and go out there
and and do it than watching, you know.
So, it's a it's a fun thing to be a part
of. Um, you can make it stressful or you
can make it, uh, you know, calm and
collected. And I feel like that's what
we were today. I thought our guys on the
outside and up front did a hell of a job
um, on that last drive and I just try to
put in good spots.
>> What happened to your hand? What
happened to your hand? And did that
affect your ability?
>> Yeah, I [clears throat] got a finger
bent back. They saw it on the um you
know on the TV on the sideline or
whatever. I didn't obviously know
exactly what had happened. Um it wasn't
it wasn't pleasant. Wasn't great. Um
we'll see what it what it is. Um was
obvious obviously able to finish the
game and throw it decent. Um you know
once the ball snapped, the adrenaline's
pretty good. So we'll hopefully uh you
know just keep it going.
>> With all your comebacks, what is it
[clears throat] for you about doing this
in the playoffs that you said you enjoy
and you're not nervous?
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, I I mean that's what you
work for, right? Like you do all these
hours in your life of, you know, being a
kid in the backyard throwing the ball
around saying, "Okay, this is the
situation. We got to make it happen."
And then get to do it throughout my
football career. Um, and an opportunity
like tonight, I walked behind Teddy on
the way out and was like for that last
drive, I forget what I said to him, but
I was like, "Let's go snatch these guys,
you know, like let's go snatch this one
back, man. Let's go." And, uh, you know,
he was an integral part to that drive.
Puke was, I mean, Kobe, our backs,
everybody. So, um, no, I don't know. I
just I love those situations. Um, I live
to to do it. It's great to do it on the
road, too. Quite a nice crowd today. So,
u, we'll take it.
>> Hell of a play. I thought he was going
to go up there and kind of post up, you
know, and I was like, "All right, let's
see what you got." And I threw it and
right as I cut it loose, he kind of
turned away and it was just tough
timing. U, but what a what a play to go
fight through it and get that thing
knocked out. Um, huge play for us.
>> Thanks, guys.
>> Thanks,
said you couldn't quite remember what he
told you, but he said something about
let's go snatch these guys out. What did
he say and what did you see? Yeah, I
think he said, "Let's go snatch these
guys' hearts." And that was that was
pretty uh that was pretty cold.
[clears throat] That was pretty cold
just to hear that. And I actually like
literally smiled in the moment cuz I
thought that that was like one of the
most gangster things you could say in
that moment honestly. And to hear him
say that and the look in his on his face
and then throw the touchdown and then
the look on his face after that was just
like MVP stuff.
>> In what way does that recalibrate your
guys' mindset and attitude quarterback
like him as his
Well, that's been the theme of basically
how what how I've spoken about him all
season, you know, ever since I think it
was Tennessee where he threw that pick
and then just, you know, began to just
go about his business like that never
happened. I I almost was like, did he
throw the pick? Like I had to like think
about it just based off of how he just
as as cool as he is and and just poised,
you know, and that keeps everybody else
together, especially in moments like
that where, you know, we can easily let
things get out of control and start
scrambling, trying to do too much. and
just the way he kind of operates. Um,
you know, like I said last week, it's
when when your fe when your fearless
leader is locked in and confident like
that, it just radiates throughout the
huddle and you feel it in moments like
that with this team.
>> How did you feel throughout the game and
then in during that final drive?
>> Um, as far as what
>> just your first game back, you know, did
did you feel like you just
>> picked up where you left off or did it
take you a while to kind of get a feel?
Yeah, I mean it's every game is
different, so it's I don't think
necessarily you can attribute certain
things to rust or whatever. Like I think
next [clears throat] week obviously I
you know the more we get back into it
and get into a rhythm playing together
again, you know, it'll just continue to
get better. But um yeah, I feel like I
could have played better today
personally. But um you know, we we had a
few opportunities that were some some
good ones and we had some ones that that
weren't as good. But all that matters in
these type of moments is how you can,
you know, come together as a team,
especially at this point in the year.
Like the all pros and all that stuff is
already out there. Pro Bowl is already
set. So, it's just time to play team
ball and see who can do that the best
and and end up uh, you know, where we
where we ultimately want to be at the
end.
>> You guys have had a couple of games this
year that were similar where you're up
two touchdowns or double digits and then
you're down and you don't win. Yeah.
>> What did you like that was different
today?
>> I like that we won.
>> Yeah. That's that's is way better.
Obviously, in any situation, you always
want to play the cleanest game possible.
Go down and and put them away. You know,
situations where the defense is is
playing really good early. You want to,
you know, have those those games where
you just go and just continue to score.
And when you look across, you know,
around the huddle that we have is
there's really no excuse to not go and
do it. And, um, I think we have so much
confidence that sometimes we got to, you
know, realize the other team has a say.
You know, it's it's a it's playoff
football and and, you know, they're a
really good team as well. So, um it's
not always going to go your way, but we
have that confidence that we can and you
know, as long as we keep that mindset,
stay healthy, and just go out and keep
attacking the way we can, um you know,
we we got the confidence we can win any
game.
>> You talked about how fun this season has
been for you. Uh just with that in mind,
what was it like to be a part of this
game uh in a performance like this and
to be able to extend that season for
another week?
>> It's awesome. I mean, for me, I'm
especially grateful for it not having
been to the playoffs since my last year
with the Packers and you know, that was
that was a while ago now. So, um, you
know, I was I was fired up for this game
and and excited to come out here, make
some plays, and, you know, be excited
for my teammates when they make those
plays. So, it's, uh, it's a great
feeling, obviously, just to keep playing
ball at this point of the year. Um,
meaningful, you know, January, February
ball is what it's all about. That's what
you, that's what you work the whole year
for. Um, so it's a good feeling.
>> What was Sean?
Um, just basically, you know, we if if
we want to continue to to, you know,
have this feeling that we have after
this game, we just got to keep locking
in and and and playing as good as we
possibly can out there and as clean as
we can, you know, taking advantage of
the basically what I said a moment ago,
taking advantage of the opportunities
where, you know, we can put teams like
that away and um but also not to forget
how special it is to be able to come in
here on the road and and win a game like
that in the playoffs. Doesn't matter who
you're playing against. So, um, can't
lose sight of that part.
bloodied after that hit from Scott,
tongue.
>> Yeah, a little bit of everything. Yeah,
it was the head was fine. It was more my
jaw kind of you get caught in a weird
way. The my jaw felt a little weird and
then um yeah, bloody tongue a little bit
and and bit the inside of my mouth. But
yeah, we all right.
Yeah. Um,
guy played it really well. Honestly, he
played over the top. It's a a double
move and um I knew it was going to have
to be a back shoulder ball and and
Matthew placed it perfectly. You know,
he couldn't have walked up and and put
it any better. Um just gave me a chance
and you know, obviously all that starts
with a great drive to lead up to that
point. O line playing great, protecting
very well. So, thank you for the
opportunity.
>> Did you catch it? [laughter]
>> I said, "Yeah, why is no one
celebrating? I'm in. Come on."
Stafford was saying that yeah, you
looked very confident that he didn't
know.
>> Yeah. I mean, that's kind of how you can
tell if if someone caught the ball or
not. Uh is based off how they celebrate.
You know, they can go to review and
whatnot, but if someone celebrates right
away, you typically know that they
caught the ball.
>> What was it like in the huddle in that
final drive? Stafford apparently had
said, you know, let's rip their hearts
out right before that drive.
>> Yeah. Um, Higgby started the drive off,
did a great job in those first few plays
and, um, I was able to go in and, uh,
just kind of witness, yeah, Matthew just
taking complete control and, uh, just a
ton of fun and just knowing that you
have so much trust in a guy like that to
to lead you is is great.
>> What is it about this uh, passing game
between you guys as tight ends, Matthew,
[snorts]
and Devonte, where you can have
stretches of the game where you're maybe
not playing your best, but like when you
have to turn it on, you guys can turn it
on.
>> Yeah. I mean, I feel like you've seen
that time in and time out this season is
when you need it most, we're able to go
down and make a make a drive and um you
know, those guys on the edge are doing
such a great job. Hookah and Dvonte and
the whole receiver core, it it opens up
everything for us, too. So, when we play
complimentary football, I think we're a
tough team to beat.
>> What was it like having this performance
today? Not only just as a continuation
of what you've been able to contribute,
but you also having, you know, family in
attendance.
>> Yeah, I was overwhelming. Yeah, I mean,
God is so good. I'm so blessed to be in
this position and um every good and
perfect gift is from the Lord and I
believe that wholeheartedly and um it
was pretty cool after I caught the
touchdown say on the sideline I just
looked up at my family and had shed a
few tears. Yeah, it was pretty cool.
Pretty special.
>> All right, thanks guys.